Guide to the Michael M. May Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Meetings, Grants, Proposals
  - Workshop on Protecting and Assuring Critical National Infrastructure: Next Steps (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - SU Harvard Def Proj Caucasus in 21st Century March 31, 98 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Prev. Def. Conf Apr 3-4 '98 Perry/Carter at SU (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lockheed Talk 4/16/98 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Deana Arsenian 5/4/98 Carnegie (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - A/PARC-Hoover Meeting 5/14-5/15/98 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - LLNL E. Asian Mtg on Nuc. Saf./Coop. 5/98 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - May 11 Lederberg (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - CFR Study Grp China/Asia Energy Demand (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - ASPEN Mtg (WS) July 14-24 '98 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Amer. All. 8/20-22/98 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Tokyo Aug 28-98 Urg Conf Nuke Non-Prolif/Disarm. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Protocol Mtg 9/17-9/18/98 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Peacebuilding as Prevention (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Bechtel Affair BIGGC Oct 19-20 98 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - PAC Council Retreat Oct 16-18 98 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - EPRI Meeting 11/2/98 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Nov 12 98 New Orleans (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - BCW Conf (Hoover) Drell Nov 16-18/98 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - RAND Adv. 11/17/98 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Drell Symposium SLAC 7/31/98 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Affiliate Seminar + WS 12/1/98 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Oksenberg - International Diplomacy Council (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Dec 1998 (SAGAN) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 12/1/98 Affil WS "US Export Control Policy: The Case of Foreign Launched Satellites" (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Beijing Trip May 16-21/1997 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Vietnam Trip 4/2-4/15-'97 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Crisp WS Apr 20 99 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Research Sem 4-28-99 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - APARC Conf May 3 99 8-5 Bechtel (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - European Forum Conf May 10-11 1999 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Spr Sum 1999 WS to further Intl. Assur. of Fissil Mat'l Sec. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Caspian Reg. Conf 5/13-5/14/99 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - UCSD Talk May 17 1999 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - CGSR Workshop 6/2-6/4/99 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Forrest Frank Visit June 11 99 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Trip to DC end June 99 Mike (Mary) + Chi (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Foster Panel July 12-13 1999 LLNL Nuke Wpn Stkpl (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - A/PARC WS 7/23/99 World Bank Strategy OKIMOTO (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Affiliate Prog New Century Seminars 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - NAS Find. the Balance Aug 2-4 99 WDC (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - AAAS Meeting 8/31/99W, DC (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Chron 1998 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - May Chron 1999 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - May Recvd 1999 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - May Chron 2003 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Tech-Side Devel. of CISAC (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - AMEX Claim 8-11-01 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - May Chron 2002 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - May Chron 2001 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - 2000 Chron May (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Regrets 99-00 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Received Misc. (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Visitor (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Gift (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Who's Who Sci + Eng (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Mike - Correspondences (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - May Chron (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Robin Grp Sept 17-19 97 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Beijing-Shanghai Trip 1/5/96 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Nuclear Materials Stewardship Workshop 10/28-29/96 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Beijing-Fudan Trip 1/5/96-1/13/96 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Beijing Talk-1/8/96 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - May Talk 11/30/96 Who Will Keep the Nuclear Peace (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Wheelon Lecture 11/96 Robert Gallucci (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Wheelon Lecture 1/98 Josh Lederberg (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Wheelon Lecture 11/95 David Hamburg (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Drell Lecture 1998 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Wheelon/Drell Lectureship 98-99 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - John M. Deutch Photo/Bio Materials (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Deutch Dinner (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Drell Lec 3/4/99 5pm (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Deutch Small Group (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Deutch Agenda (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Oshita (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Chi Zhang Talk/Visit (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Xiao Chen (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Energy Infrastructure Proposal (HM proposal) (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Energy Group Seminar (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Research (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Cox Report Discussion (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Dean Wilkening "Nuclear Warfare" (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Wilkening Reappointment 2002 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - (M May) Wilkening (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Ref Response (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Wilkening Reappt (Box 7, Folder 89)
- Trips, Drafts, Reports
  - Berkeley VU (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 4/20/98 Berkeley Talk (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - May US Foreign Policy + Nuclear Disarmament 4/16/98 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 4/28/99 CISAC Seminar NW + US Strategy (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Strategy Paper Comment (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - US Strat + NW Annotated UCSD IR/PS May 17 99 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - VU Graphs 4/28/99 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - USS + NW Apr-Jul 99 Material (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Non Prolif Var Views LONDON IIIS 12/2-3/99 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 11/29/99 PARIS disc on Cerela Militaire (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Grand Strategy LA Times 7/99 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Great Power Rivalries UCSD 01/02/27 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Econ Sec Seminar Spr 93 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Economic Security Seminar '91 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - UCSD US China Econ Sec Rev Commis. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Statement to House Armed Services Committee, 4/8/92 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Oslo Mtg 6/24/92 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Sep 92 NW Talk Shanghai (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - "Role of US N/W in Reg. Confl." W/ R. Speed 1993 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Demand for Wpns Seattle Ans July 93 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Demand for NW + US Policy Jan-Dec 93 TLK and ASH Carter Input (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Tech Sem CISAC on AMSCI 9/27/94 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Cameron on Dec. to Prolif. or not (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - "Nukes" 5/25/95 Brkgs. Rev. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - APARC - Foreign Direct Investment in New Electricity Generating Capacity in Developing Asia: Stakeholders, Risks, and the Search for a NEw Paradigm - Robert Thomas Crow (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Environmental Presentations - Technology Strategies and Global Climate Change Policy (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Workshop East Asia (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - A/PARC alliances Mtg. Aug. 22-23, 97 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - VGs - E&S EA - CISAC 10/15/97 PS125 11/24/97 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - China Energy & Security TLK ESE 70116 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Energy & Security in East Asia 1998 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - GHG Emission Baselines in China (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - CGSR - Whither Deterrence? (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Aspen Global Change Institute (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - 7/7 W/S Meeting (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Electricity Choices and Carbon Emissions in Guangdong Province (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - DOE/IGCC Mtg 8/19/96 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Asia Pacific Coop'n Meeting Nov 96 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - IR/PS Talk GRT PWRS INEA Sept 28, 96 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - JS Choi Reg COMACT EA (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Senchiao (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Washington Quarterly (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Talk 5/14/99 Caspian (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Woodrow Wilson Center US-China Relations 7/2/97 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Guangzhou Talk (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Energy and SEcurity Paper Lewis 12/12/01 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - UCSD 1/16/97 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - APRC 3/24/97 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Washington DC Trip April 22-23, 97 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - EA Nuc Coop (LLNL) 5/30/97 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Beijing Mtgs on Energy 18-21 May 1997 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Comm. on US Pac Trade + Inv SF 6/30/97 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Statute of IAEA 6/14/57 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ebenhausen Mtg 10/23-25/94 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Mtg IMRSS (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Aix-en-Provence Mtg IMRSS 11/9-10/95 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - DC DOE SAIC, LANL Mtg 1/8/97 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Materials Stewardship (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Compliance/Verification (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Lab Talk, Beijing Sep 92 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Japan Talk APRC 11/21/94 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - IGC 50112 Japan Tlk (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Senbei Beijing 4/20/95 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Beijing NEACD 1/8-10/96 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - IMRSS (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Beck Report (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Global 2001 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Russian White Paper on Nuclear Weapons (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - John Taylor "Reprocessing Economics" (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Reactor Grade Pu in Wpns (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - "Left" Plutonium (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Tons/Tons, Tons/Gwyz, etc. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 12/8/93 LLNL/DOE TLK on World Energy Growth (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Sem. on CISAC Pu Study (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 3/29-30/WS on Civ Pu JJ Taylor on Reprocess. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - April 94 Tlk on Inputs to US Policy on Pu (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Amer. Sci. Drafts 1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Pu DC WS VG's 6/16/94 Discussion Session on the Future of Civilian Plutonium (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Proliferation-Resistant Nuclear Power Systems, June 2-4, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - USA v. Wen Ho Lee Court Records (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - 4/00 NAS-APS Tlk (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Committee of 100 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Wen Ho Lee (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Cox Com Report, Press (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Cox Report, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - The Cox Committee Report: An Assessment (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Cox Rep't Rep't (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Cox Rep't Material (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Soph Sem Agendas (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - "Arms Control Today" (Soph Sem) (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - "American Scientist" (Soph Sem) (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Domenici Article/Statement (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Rossin (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - "Flawed Case for Nuc Disarmament" (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - "Global Energy & Electricity Futures" Chauncey Starr (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Nuclear Safeguards Non-Prolif. Nuc. (Soph Sem) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - India Nuclear Test (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - "Population and the Energy Problem" John P Holdren (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - "Nuclear News" Seville: Low Level Radiation (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - PHYSICS TODAY Articles (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - "Science, Technology, and the Nuclear Arms Race" Schroeer (soph sem) (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Wilkening article (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - "How a Nuclear Plant Works" (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - NSA M. May (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 2DKL701 NSA Contract Expenditure Reports (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1998 NSA Sy Goodman (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Goodman Reimbursement for Dec. Conference (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Karen Fusilier (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - CRISP Pubs Activities 97-00 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - NSA Proposal May, Feigenbaum (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - CRISP (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - NSA WGIT (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - NSA Assorted (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - NSA Proposal (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1998 CSI/FBI Computer Crime + Security Survey (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - NSA Employee, etc. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - CRISP Rebudgeting & No Cost Extension 2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - The Global Diffusion of the Internet Project: An Initial Inductive Study, 22 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Cybercrime Conference CRISP/Hoover (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Protecting Cyberspace: the International Dimension (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - List of Attendees Affiliates Mtg Dec 1, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - April 20 National Plan Review (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - April 20 National Plan Review (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - List of Participants (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Dec 7th ABSTRACTS (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Dec 7th Workshop (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Dec 7 Background (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Dec 7th Report (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Nat'l/Internat'l Security Issues Proposal (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - CREES - A History (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Others' Comments (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Foreign Affairs 5/96 Rivalries paper (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Partn. for Peace Protocol Mtg. 5/24-25/94 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - FRS Mtg Paris 020926-7 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Prague-Budapest 12/15-23/90 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - "Nuclear Wpns in Europe" w/ K. Smith (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - NATO - DFT Commentary (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Christopher on Human Rights NYT 6/15/93 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Baruch Plan (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Perceived Time M3 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Science Piece (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Is Ltr Re-Japan (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Diocese of Oakland & IGCC Conference 10/2/92 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Op Eds (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Bosnia Conf 4 May 93 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Running Against Public Good 5/16/95 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - US Nat'l Inter. + Moral Position CISAC 6/28/94 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Lockheed Talk 3/13/03 M. May (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - LLNL Retirees Talk (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Ocean Mixing: Holdren (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Criticality in Repositories (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Sutcliffe on Pu-Risks (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Huang Renwei - TMD Outline (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - War on Terrorism Talk 10/10/01 CISAC (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - SCCN Seminar 5/02/28 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Prague CEU Tlk (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - LANL TALK GM3 8/30/95 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Monterey NPG Conf 9/14-15/95 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Protocol Meeting Oct. 18, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Sandia Tlk 11/30/95 Who Will Keep Nuclear Peace? (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Shanghai Fudan U Tlk 1/12/96 on Rivalries + NW (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Les Amis 3/20/96 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - CISAC on GM 4/3/96 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - APSA Mts 8/29/96 "Rivalries + Power Projection" (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Nucl. Deter. E. Peace 5/28/97 Major Power (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - GMDF's + Kuchins Comments (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - "Rivalries" Final Summary (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - The National Interest (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Photos 11/99 China E WS (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - China Energy Nov 99 Workshop (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Workshop Report Nov 1999 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Articles, Misc (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Effectiveness of Nuclear Weapons Against Buried Biological Agents (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Carbon Intensity of Electricity Generation + CDM Baseline: Case Studies of Three Chinese Provinces (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists March/April 2005 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Impact on Global Warming of Development and Structural Changes in the Electricity Sector of Guangdong Province, China (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Verifying the Agreed Framework (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Energy Policy Vol. 29 No. 3 Feb 2001 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - 6/19/00 LLNL mtg re OPRK KEDO security and safeguards (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - KEDO (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - DPRK W/S 1/31-2/1/01 Presentation (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - World Inventory of Plutonium and Highly Enriched Uranium, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Dose Rates Fr. Spent Fuel (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Dautray Report on Nuclear Power (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Tabulations of Nuclear Facilities (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - The Long-Term Program for Development and Utilization of Nuclear Energy - Draft Translation (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Department of Energy (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - NAS Openness Com. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Striving for Long-Term Energy Security: Japan's Policy on the Use of Plutonium (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Japan Pu (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Plutonium Spring 1994 No. 5 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - World Energy: The Facts and the Future (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Japan - Nuc En - Treaties (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Reactors - Japan (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Holdren Bunn on Pu (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - NMD Conf Stanford Nov 19-20 '00 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Agendas & Administrative (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - NAS Correspondence Future Activities (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Moscow Meeting - Notes et al. 3/93 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - NAS: German Report (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - NAS: "Balancing" 1999 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Non-Prolif. WS 3/1/2004 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Lab Directors (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - File ISODARCO 2000 Italy (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Export Control W/S 6/7/00 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Satellite Exports Control Affiliates Workshop 12/1/98 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - LLNL DC April 30, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory 1/8/1998 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Tlk LLNL WA 7/25/96 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - LLNL Security (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Gofman "Early Years" 1995 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Classif Policy Stat. 7/28/95 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Robin Group (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - LLNL Seminar May 11-13 1998 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - KYL (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - RAND Board of Trustees (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - 1994 Rgs Qual. Ex. (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - RAND Graduate School (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - UCSD 00 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - IISS 1998 Annual Conference (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - EPRI Meeting 7/13/98 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Protocol Mtg 9/18/98 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - DPRK AF (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - SJ Merc Agreement (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Goldschmidt Letter (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - LWR Safeguards (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - KEDO Misc (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - WS on Safeguarding DPRK Reactors Under the Agreed Framework (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - The Structure + Content of Agreements btwn the Agency + States REquired in Connection with the Treaty on the Non-Proliferation of Nuclear Weapons (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Roundtable Discussioin on the Comprehensive Test Ban Treaty, Stanford University July 19, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Argonne Talk 01-05-20 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Suti - LLNL (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Lewis's Asia Mtgs (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Verifying the AF - Distribution (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Reports (Restricted)